结束函数得到背包给我们
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Closure functions
getting back packs give our
功能持久的记忆。
functions persistent memories.
看看这个,
Look at this,
我的新功能有一个永久性的数据存储。
my new function has a persistent store
of data attached to it permanent.
它就在附近，哪儿也去不了，一个隐藏处,
It sticks around,
it's not going anywhere, a cache,
数据的永久存储为编写专业代码提供了全新的工具包。
permanent store of data gives entirely new
toolkit for writing professional code.
首先是辅助函数，你可以在挑战中看到它们,
So firstly helper functions,
you see them in the challenges,
普通的专业耳机，就像一旦你记住。
everyday professional headphones,
like once you memorize.
让我们花点时间来看看这些。
Let's actually take
a second to look at these.
所以一旦记住了，他就是一个例子。
So once a memorize,
he would be an example.
也许我可以用红色，让我看看。
Maybe I can use red, let's see.
所以如果我做一个1到5的乘以2,
So if I were to do a one to five
version of multiply by two,
我第一次运行它的时候，输入7乘以2。
the first time I run it multiply
by two with the input of seven.
它会给我14。
It would give me out 14.
下次我运行它的时候，如果输入10，它就会发出 sorry，或者
Next time I run it, with the input
of ten it would give out sorry, or
这样的事情，你不能再控制我了。
something like that,
you can't run me again.
因为当我运行它的时候,
Because when I ran it,
我会在运行另一个返回函数的运行程序中创建它。
I would have created it inside the runner
running another function returned out.
然后我把它扔回柜台上。
And I throw it back over the counter.
当我运行它的时候，我写的逻辑是它做乘法运算，但是
When I run it I written the logic
that it does the multiplication, but
然后在背包里增加账户。
then it increments
accounts in the backpack.
下次我运行它时，它会检查那个背包。
Next time I run it,
it checks that backpack.
伯爵已经是一个了。
Count is already one.
而不是做数学回报抱歉。
And instead of even doing
the math returns out sorry.
它可能通常不这样做，而是实际上可能通常存储值
It might typically instead to do this it
might actually typically store the value
14个，还有大概一包。
of 14 and about pack.
下一次，它会返回原来的值。
And next time,
it's gonna return on that original value.
这在实践中非常有用。
This is super useful in practice.
显然不是绝望的这一个，但超级有用的实践。
Obviously not desperate for this one,
but super useful in practice.
如果你正在构建任何你想锁定的应用程序
If you're building any App where
you want to lock down maybe for
例如一个获胜的功能，当应用程序完成游戏结束。
example like a winning function, that when
the apps finish the game is finished.
你不希望有人，重新运行那个函数，你希望这样做
And you want you don't want to have
someone, rerun that function, you want to
锁定该函数，它只能运行一次，它的制胜功能。
lock that function down it can only be
run once it's the winning function.
这是一个函数，当某人赢得比赛时，所有的一切都会触发
It's a function that when the when
somebody won the game triggers all the all
比如，关于赢不赢井字棋的事。
the stuff to do on winning or
not it tic tac toe, for example.
您不希望能够重置单元格中的任何值。
You don't wanna be able to reset
any of the values in the cells.
一旦它有一个 o，它就被锁定了，你不能再运行它了。
Once it's got an o, it's locked down,
you can't run it again.
一旦它找到一个真正的干净和
Once it finds a really clean and
可读的方式锁定代码，而不是运行它多次，这是有点不错。
readable way of locking down code to not
run it multiple times, that's kinda nice.
记忆，标准的计算机科学实践,
Memorization, standard
computer science practice,
如果我有一个这样的任务，这开始成为
of saying, if I have a task like,
that's starting to become
我通过 tall 得到的太多信息就像是找到了最终的素数。
my [LAUGH] too much information via tall
is like finding the end prime number.
任何慢投和质数都可以，假设是127,000。
Any in slow toss and prime number
that's fine suppose like 127,000.
很明显，我的随机数生成不是很好。
Okay, clearly my random number
generation is not very good.
我得到了编码127,000中最少的随机数之一。
I've got one of the least random
numbers in coding 127,000.
第一，如果我想找到这个质数,
And one,
if I try to find that prime number,
第127,000个质数，这需要一点时间。
the 127,000th prime number,
that's gonna take a bit of time.
但在我的运行时间，在我的应用程序，如果我运行一次，它可能会再次发生。
But in my run time, in my app,
if I run it once, it may happens again.
我不会经常关闭我的应用程序并重新启动它。
I'm not turning my app off and
starting it again very often.
所以如果我运行一次，我可能需要再运行一次，通常是这样。
So if I run it once,
I may need to run it again, typically.
我需要重新计算吗？
Do I wanna recalculate that?
或者我想把第 n 个基本功能定义，放入一个背包
Or do I want to have that nth prime
function definition have a backpack into
我有一个带键和值对的对象，每次运行它的时候
which I have an object with key and
value pairs where every time I run it with
一个输入，当我第一次用一个输入运行它的时候，我做了艰苦的工作，弄清楚。
an input, first time I run it with
an input, I do the hard work, figure out.
我不知道，也许是第 n 个质数，也许是第827,000或者
I don't know, maybe the nth prime number,
maybe the 827,000th or
第一个素数，我不知道，不管它是什么。
first prime numbers I don't know,
whatever it is.
然后，在函数的背包中的键值对中,
And then, in my key value pairs
in the backpack of the function,
我会得到一个键127,001和一个质数的值。
I'm going to have a key 127, 001 and
a value of whatever that prime number is.
127,000第一个素数，也许是我不知道。
The 127,000 1st prime number,
maybe it's I don't know.
很好，也许是257,133。
That's good.
Maybe get 257,133.
这就对了，高风险。
There you go, high risk there.
正在安装。
It is installing that.
下次我运行这个函数的时候,
Next time I run the function, and prime,
要么说明我对质数一无所知。
that either shows I have no
idea about prime numbers or.
下次我用这个输入来写函数的时候。
Next time I write the function
with that with that inputs.
我不会再从头开始想了。
I ain't gonna figure it out
myself from scratch again.
我去看看背包。
I'm going to go look in the backpack.
检查一下已经完成了，那是什么？
Check it's been done with, what was that?
只需要一个步骤，一个眼神，抓住，然后返回，非常好。
And with one step, one look up,
grab and return, super nice.
这就是记忆的概念，赋予我们功能
This is the notion of memorization,
giving our functions
以前输入输出组合的持久记忆。
persistent memories of their
previous input output combinations.
这是非常有效的。
And that's super effective.
但是还有更多的迭代器和生成器。
But there's more iterators and generators.
不是一个愿望就是用词汇范围的圈地来达到最大的目的
Wasn't a wish use lexical scoping
enclosure to achieve the most
现代的。
contemporary.
这是一个非常空洞的陈述。
It's a very empty statement.
它们是某种完整的部分，新的坚硬的部分，他看到了它。
They are something in whole parts,
new hard parts he was seeing it.
我认为这是一种非常优雅的访问数据的方式。
I think this is a very elegant
way of accessing data.
所以我们看到早期的完整循环是一个痛苦的屁股。
So we saw early the full
loop is a pain in the ass.
我不在乎索引,
I don't really care about the index,
我关心的是数组在该位置的值，即元素。
I care about the value in that
position of the array, the element.
如果我能创建一个函数,
Well, it wouldn't be amazing if I
could creat a function that when run,
它给出了我右边的第一个元素？
it gives me out the first
element in my right?
再次运行它，它的输出是下一个元素，再次运行它，它的输出是
Run it again, its output is the next
element, run it again its output is
接下来，它是如何记住之前给出的前一个元素的？
the next, how's it remembering
previously giving out previous element?
不要担心，在背包里它存放在小柜台上，跟踪
Don't worry, in the backpack it store
in little counter that's tracking
通过潜在的数据。
through the underlying data.
产生这样的说法是一个更大的水平。
Generating say that's
an even larger level.
如果我真的可以暂停一个函数的运行会怎么样？
What if I could actually appear to
pause the running of a function?
或者它运行的是什么函数？
Or what is it running a function?
它的内存和函数中的线性。
Well, its memory and
the liner in the function.
就是这样，如果我回到函数,
That's it,
if I were to come back to a function,
我只需要记忆中的东西。
all I need is what was in the memory.
当我还是我的时候,
And while I was I on a generation,
它说你回来继续运行一个函数，怎么做？
it says you come back to
continue running a function, how?
因为它存储了所有的实时数据。
Because it stored all the live data.
在背包里，意思是当你回来后再开始运行它。
In the backpack, meaning when you
come back and start running it again.
它只是从背包里拿出一天的时间，里面有你所有的数据
It just grabs a day from the backpack and
there is all your data is you went and
你又回来了。
you are back in the function.
模块模式，对吗？
Module pattern, right?
这真的很有趣。
This is really interesting.
我们希望数据能够持续到应用程序的生命周期。
We want to have data that persists for
the lifespan of application.
我们通常把它放在哪里？
Where can we normally puts it?
我们不能把它放在函数调用中，因为它会被删除。
We can not put it inside a function
call because he gets deleted.
一旦退出函数，他就将其放入 global 中。
Once you exit the function,
he put it in global.
但是在大量的基础代码中，有100,000行代码和100个视图
But in a lot of code base with that
100,000 lines of code with 100 view
说唱歌手。
rappers.
你不会让全球记忆被全球标签所污染
You ain't having global memory
polluted with the global label
结果就是你的团队得到了很大的发展，他们喜欢这个标签。
results as a lot of developing
your team who love that label.
你知道宣布与汗的帮助有些，但
And you know declaring with
Khan's help somewhat but
只是现在没有人能在全球范围内宣布。
just now no one else can
declare it globally.
我觉得这样好多了。
I think that much better.
所以我们用设计模式来保存实时数据的状态
So instead we have design patterns that
preserved state that's live data for
在不污染全局名称空间的情况下保持应用程序的有效性,
the life of your application without
polluting the global namespace,
多种模式。
multiple patterns.
其中之一就是其中的许多。
One of them is many of them.
如果他做到了同样的事情，他们在做什么？
If he's achieved the same thing,
what are they doing?
模型专利在做什么？
What's the model patent doing?
你知道它在做什么，就是在背包里保护国家。
You know what it's doing,
is protecting state inside backpacks.
它说有一种方法可以维持应用生命的状态。
It saying there is a way of maintaining
state for the life of application.
那是魔法，或者根本不是魔法。
And that's by the magic,
or not magic at all.
这是通过数据的保护，可以接口，但
That's by having data that is protected,
can be interfaced with, but
只有通过一个非常非常干净的界面来运行这个函数。
only through a very, very clean
interface of running that function.
并确保你通过正确的东西，以获得访问，并
And making sure you pass in
the right stuff, to get access, and
在背包中存储和保存数据。
store and persist data in the backpack.
节点模块模式只是在背包中使用闭包。
And the node module pattern is all
just using closure In the backpack.
你可以看到这个 JavaScript。
And you see this JavaScript.
我们明天再来看看
We'll see to it tomorrow, call-backs and
如果是这个州，所有的承诺都依赖于结束。
promises also all rely on
closure if it's this state.
这意味着同步工作，我们将在明天看到,
What this means is in a sync job,
which we'll see tomorrow,
你经常送出一个任务，这个任务在未来很长一段时间都不会完成。
you often send off a task that's
gonna complete long in the future.
当这样做的时候，你要在这些数据上运行一个函数。
When it does, you're going to
run a function on that data.
你可能想要使用最初设置这个函数时存在的数据
And you may want to use data that was
there when that function was initially set
抛球最初是这样安排的。
up and the toss was initially set up.
但是等等，那一天已经过去了，不是吗？
But hold on,
that day's all gone, hasn't it?
不，这些可以使用的数据被保存在功能背包里。
Nope, that data that could ever be used
is held on into the functions backpack.
这意味着当我们最终运行这个函数时，例如，我们去
Meaning when we end up running
the function, for example, we go and
和推特联系带回推文,
speak to Twitter, bring back send tweets,
触发一个函数来自动运行这些 tweets。
trigger a function to run
automatically on those tweets.
也许它需要一些当初定义这个函数时就存在的数据
Maybe it needs some data that was there
when that function was initially defined
和 Twitter 的对话任务已经建立，但是数据还在吗？
and the speak to Twitter task was set up,
but it that data still there?
当然是了。
Well, of course it is.
别担心，因为它就储存在背包里。
Don't worry,
cuz it's stored in the backpack.